itcinfotech.com 2018-07-17

# ITC Infotech Privacy Policy: ITC Infotech

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Statement is effective as of May 2018

#### OBJECTIVE

We respect an individual's right to privacy and are committed to protecting the privacy of personal information supplied to us either by an individual or others. This Policy lays down our practices regarding collection and use of your personal data and sets forth your privacy rights. This Policy applies to information supplied to us on our website.  
We may use personal information provided to us for any of the purposes as set out in this Policy, or as otherwise disclosed at the point of collection.

#### DEFINITIONS

"Personal information" or “Personal data” means any information that relates to a natural person, which, either directly or indirectly, in combination with other information available or likely to be available with a body corporate, is capable of identifying such person.

"We," "us," and "our" (and other similar terms) refer to ITC Infotech India Limited, its subsidiaries, and subsidiaries of its subsidiaries, if any.

“You” and “your” (and other similar terms) refer to our clients, individuals associated with our clients, contacts, suppliers, job applicants, staff and visitors to our website.

#### INFORMATION COLLECTION & SHARING

We only collect information that you voluntarily and knowingly supply to us (e.g., through filling out contact forms, sign-ups on the career portal, or other interaction with the website).

Some of this information that you may provide will identify you personally, either alone or in combination with other information available with us.

We may also collect certain information through cookies that, like most web servers, we transmit via our cookie folder from the browser on the hard disk of your computer, to recognize your device during a session or in your future visits to our website, primarily to provide better user experience. Please read our [Cookie Policy](https://www.itcinfotech.com/cookie-policy/) carefully for more details about the information we collect when you use this website.

An option is made available for you to sign in or create accounts on the career portal through social websites such as Facebook, LinkedIn, and Twitter or the like. The terms and conditions applying to the personal information supplied through such websites are based on the Privacy terms you agree on such social websites. You are requested to verify their Privacy terms before providing your personal information to us via such social websites. We do not have any association or control over the use of your personal information by such social websites.

We will only process the personal information where we have a lawful reason for doing so, where the processing is necessary to pursue our legitimate business interests (including maintaining repository of potential candidates for jobs, promotion of our services and where so authorized by you on the website to establish communication with prospective clients with general/ business inquiries).

#### REASONABLE SECURITY PRACTICES & PROCEDURES

To prevent unauthorized disclosure or access of the personal information we have in place appropriate security practices and procedures comprising of managerial, technical, operational and physical security controls to protect your personal data from unauthorized or inappropriate access, alteration, disclosure, and destruction.

#### INFORMATION SHARING

The personal information we collect from you is stored in one or more cloud-based databases hosted by third parties which may be located outside your home country, in the United States, in India or other locations. The third parties do not use or have access to your personal data for any purpose other than cloud storage, retrieval or maintenance activities.

We have offices and operations in a number of international [locations](https://www.itcinfotech.com/location/), and we share information between our group companies for business and administrative purposes.

Where required or permitted by law, information may be provided to others, such as regulators and law enforcement agencies.

From time to time, we may consider corporate transactions such as a merger, acquisition, reorganization, asset sale, or similar. In these instances, we may transfer or allow access to information to enable the assessment and undertaking of that transaction. If we buy or sell any business or assets, personal data may be transferred to third parties involved in the transaction.

Where the personal data is supplied to us by you from EU and where we transfer personal data outside of EU, we either transfer personal data to countries that provide an adequate level of protection (as determined by the European Commission) or have appropriate safeguards in place. Appropriate safeguards to cover these transfers are in the form of standard contractual/data protection clauses adopted by the European Commission, and where transfers are to the US, we may rely on Privacy Shield certification.

#### DATA STORAGE AND RETENTION

We retain your personal information for the period for which it is reasonably necessary for the purposes mentioned above, or as required by any law in force or for audit purposes.

#### YOUR RIGHTS

You may have certain rights relating to your personal data provided for, under applicable law. These are the right to:

  * Request access to your personal data and the processing activities on the personal data
  * Request that your personal data is rectified if it is inaccurate or incomplete
  * Request erasure of your personal data in certain circumstances
  * Request restriction of the processing of your personal data in certain circumstances
  * Object to the processing of your personal data in certain circumstances
  * Receive your personal data provided to us as a controller in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format in certain circumstances
  * Lodge a complaint with supervisory authority
  * Withdraw your consent provided at any time by contacting us

To exercise the rights outlined above in respect of your personal data, please contact the Grievance Officer identified below. We will endeavor to respond to you within an appropriate time as required by the law.

#### PROTECTION OF MINOR’s INFORMATION

The website is not directed to children under the age of sixteen (16). We do not knowingly solicit personal information from or market to anyone under sixteen (16) years of age. If you believe that we have received information from a minor, please notify us immediately, and we will ensure that reasonable efforts will be made by us to delete such information from our database.

#### EXTERNAL LINKS

Our website may contain links to other websites including social media websites, event websites, etc. whose information practices may be different from ours. You should read such third party's websites privacy notices before interacting or providing any of your personal information. We do not control those websites or their privacy practices. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites.

#### CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

Please note that this Policy may change from time to time. We will provide notice, on this page, of any such changes, including the date they became effective. Please visit our website to keep abreast of any changes to the Policy.

#### GRIEVANCE REDRESSAL

The name and contact details of the Grievance Officer are provided below:

**Name:** Mr. Sanjay V Shah, Sr. VP & Company Secretary  
**Address:** ITC Infotech India Limited # 18 Banaswadi Main Road, Maruthiseva Nagar, Bengaluru-560005, Karnataka, India  
**Phone no:** +918022988235  
**Email Id:** [Sanjay.shah@itcinfotech.com](mailto:Sanjay.shah@itcinfotech.com)
